<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InfoPractices</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="practices_a">Neoris</string>
    <string name="practices_b">Accenture</string>
    <string name="practices_c">Deloitte</string>
    <string name="practices_d">Telefónica</string>
    <string name="practices_e">Indra</string>

    <string name="time_a">3 months</string>
    <string name="time_b">6 months</string>
    <string name="time_c">3-4 months</string>
    <string name="time_d">1-2 months</string>
    <string name="time_e">5-6 months</string>

    <string name="location_a">Helsinki, Finland</string>
    <string name="location_b">Berlin, Deutschland</string>
    <string name="location_c">Paris, France</string>
    <string name="location_d">Madrid, Spain</string>
    <string name="location_e">Oslo, Norway</string>

    <string name="description_a">
        Programmer practices at Neoris involve utilizing technical skills to design,
        develop, and maintain software systems. These practices include following best coding standards, conducting
        code reviews, performing testing and debugging, and collaborating with cross-functional teams.
        \n
        \n
        The focus is
        on delivering high-quality software solutions that meet business requirements and exceed customer expectations.
        \n
        \n
        Programmers at Neoris should have a strong understanding of programming languages and software development
        methodologies, and be able to work in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.
    </string>
    <string name="description_b">
        Programmer practices at Accenture involve utilizing cutting-edge technologies and
        best practices to develop innovative software solutions. These practices include following industry standards
        and guidelines, working with cross-functional teams, continuously learning and improving technical skills, and
        delivering high-quality, reliable software.
        \n
        \n
        Accenture programmers should be adaptable and have a strong
        understanding of various programming languages and software development methodologies. They should also be
        proactive in identifying and solving problems, and have a passion for delivering exceptional customer
        experiences.
        \n
        \n
        With a focus on innovation and collaboration, Accenture programmers are key to driving business
        growth and success.
    </string>
    <string name="description_c">
        Programmer practices at Deloitte focus on delivering high-quality software solutions
        that drive business value. This involves utilizing a collaborative, cross-functional approach and staying
        up-to-date with the latest technologies and programming languages.
        \n
        \n
        Deloitte programmers are expected to have a
        strong understanding of software development methodologies and the ability to work effectively with project teams.
        They should also be committed to continuous improvement, both in terms of their own skills and the software they
        are developing.
        \n
        \n
        With a focus on delivering innovative solutions and exceeding client expectations, Deloitte
        programmers play a critical role in driving business success.
    </string>
    <string name="description_d">
        Programmer practices at Telefónica are focused on delivering cutting-edge software
        solutions that meet the needs of the business and its customers. This involves staying up-to-date with the latest
        technologies, programming languages, and software development methodologies, as well as working closely with
        cross-functional teams.
        \n
        \n
        Telefónica programmers are expected to have strong technical skills and be able to work
        effectively under pressure in a fast-paced environment. They should also be proactive in identifying and solving
        problems, and be committed to continuous learning and improvement.
        \n
        \n
        With a focus on delivering high-quality, reliable
        software solutions, Telefónica programmers are key to the company\'s success and growth.
    </string>
    <string name="description_e">
        Programmer practices at Indra focus on delivering innovative software solutions that drive business value. This involves
        utilizing a collaborative, cross-functional approach, staying up-to-date with the latest technologies and programming
        languages, and continuously learning and improving technical skills.
        \n
        \n
        Indra programmers are expected to have a strong
        understanding of software development methodologies and the ability to work effectively with project teams. They should
        also be proactive in identifying and solving problems, and be committed to delivering high-quality software solutions that
        meet business requirements and exceed customer expectations.
        \n
        \n
        With a focus on innovation and collaboration, Indra programmers
        play a critical role in driving business success.
	<ul>
            <li>2 year experience in Kotlin</li>
            <li>Noticias</li>
            <li>Artículos</li>
            <li>Contacto</li>
        </ul>
    </string>

    <string name="home_a">On-site</string>
    <string name="home_b">Remote</string>
    <string name="home_c">On-site</string>
    <string name="home_d">Remote</string>
    <string name="home_e">On-site</string>


    <string name="salary_a">8.000€ - 10.000€ Gross/year</string>
    <string name="salary_b">5.000€ - 7.000€ Gross/year</string>
    <string name="salary_c">9.000€ - 10.000€ Gross/year</string>
    <string name="salary_d">11.000€ - 12.000€ Gross/year</string>
    <string name="salary_e">7.000€ - 8.000€ Gross/year</string>

    <string name="paper_a">Full time</string>
    <string name="paper_b">Part time</string>
    <string name="paper_c">Full time</string>
    <string name="paper_d">Part time</string>
    <string name="paper_e">Full time</string>
</resources>